<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pepware</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Pepware</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 11:09:36 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>#1 - Hello World</title>
      <link>/weeknotes/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 11:09:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/weeknotes/1/</guid>
      <description>Hello! @thatnatbuckley posted a weeknote to twitter the other day. I&amp;rsquo;m trying to get into the habit of doing weekly reviews, so I&amp;rsquo;m doing one as well!
What I did This was a pretty busy week! I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing a ton of neat stuff behind the scenes for my amazing new project, WeeklyProject.Club. We just hit the 200 subscriber mark and I&amp;rsquo;m super excited! I think there&amp;rsquo;s some great stuff coming down the pipe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roots pivacy policy</title>
      <link>/roots_pivacy_policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 18:52:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/roots_pivacy_policy/</guid>
      <description>Oriana House built the ROOTSApp as a Commercial app. This SERVICE is provided by Oriana House and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.
If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 13:49:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>-- Hello! My name is Sam Borick, and I&amp;rsquo;m a developer who speaks business. I&amp;rsquo;ve been building mobile apps since I was in high school. I got my start building production mobile apps when I started my first company, HungerPerks. That experience taught me that the most important thing about apps isn&amp;rsquo;t the software, it&amp;rsquo;s the understanding.
You can find me on Linkedin.
Pepware Services Simple Mobile Applications Not all apps have to be complicated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recommendations</title>
      <link>/recommendations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 13:49:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recommendations/</guid>
      <description>Devs Denovo Studios 10&amp;frasl;10 communications skills. Focused on Xamarin
Viperdev Great for Startups!
Lean Dog Custom Software Development &amp;amp; Consulting | Cleveland
Business Mentorship EXL Center More geared towards students, but they can point you at even more services
SCORE SCORE has some of the best experienced CEOs in the region ready to answer your questions
SBDC SBDC is Akron&amp;rsquo;s best kept secret.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I got where I am</title>
      <link>/articles/how-i-got-where-i-am/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 19:49:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/how-i-got-where-i-am/</guid>
      <description>I am an extraordinarily lucky individual. My main interest is crafting software that help people, and I happen to live in an economy where that is highly valued. But that doesn’t tell my whole story. How did I get here?
I recently graduated with a Bachelors Degree in Computer Science from The University of Akron. While I was at UAkron I learned all about Computer Science as a science, but I was always left wanting for something more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Shouldn’t be Cryptic</title>
      <link>/articles/crypto-shouldnt-be-cryptic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 19:44:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/crypto-shouldnt-be-cryptic/</guid>
      <description>“A Blockchain is a distributed append-only ledger that allows for an arbitrarily high number of actors achieve consensuszzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz……”
Some things are complicated, and some things are not. A hammer is a simple tool, while a car is not a simple tool. However, both solve a problem which is easy to describe. A hammer lets you hit things harder than you can with your hand. A car lets you move faster than you otherwise could using your legs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts from Graceland: An ETHMemphis retrospective</title>
      <link>/articles/ethmemphis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 19:41:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/ethmemphis/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this month I had the good fortune to be able to attend ETHMemphis, my first Ethereum Hackathon. The event took place at the FedEx Institute of Technology on the beautiful University of Memphis campus.
While I was working on my own project, a proof of concept dApp for evidence tracking, I was still able to stir around. This was my very first time being around people who are already interested in or a part of the Ethereum revolution, and there were a couple of things that caught my attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So You Want to Build an App?</title>
      <link>/articles/so-you-want-to-build-an-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 19:31:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/so-you-want-to-build-an-app/</guid>
      <description>So you’ve got an idea for an app that you think needs to exist. Or not, but in any case, you want some info on what to do with said idea.
 What things need to happen to make your idea exist?
 There are two major questions that you need to consider:
 Who is going to make it? What do you want your app to do?  Let’s start by answering the first question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Want to Win a Pitch? Ignore the Pitch.</title>
      <link>/articles/pitch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 19:25:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/pitch/</guid>
      <description>For many startups, pitch competitions are a vital source of funding. They provide access to capital, much of the time without taking equity. Plus they provide a vital arena for gathering constructive criticism on your concept.
So what can your organization do to have the best possible shot at taking home 1st place, and maybe even a big cardboard check?
Ignore the Pitch But why? Let’s first look at what pitch competitions (in general) look at:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win the pitch timeline</title>
      <link>/articles/pitch2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 19:25:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/pitch2/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s Sam&amp;rsquo;s Miricle Pitch Competition Timeline
If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for some concept stuff, checkout pitch.md
Your mission your mission is to get as much traction as possiable. traction &amp;gt; plans
EZ-PZ ways to get traction:
3 Weeks Out - Talk to People:  Survey 10+ friends if they like it Survey 10+ people who might actually want it (think internet forums &amp;amp; social media) If there is a big org you want to work with, reach out the them now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to develop new Cordova plugins for Ionic without loosing your mind</title>
      <link>/articles/cordova-plugins/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 19:21:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/cordova-plugins/</guid>
      <description>After 9 months of running a production Ionic App (HungerPerks), we finally got to the point where we needed a custom Cordova plugin, distinct enough to not be able to just fork an existing one and make changes to it. Unfortunately, all the articles, Github repos, and documentation were all some combination of outdated, incomplete, or broken.
This article will broadly discuss:
 The parts of a Cordova plugin, and where they live in an Ionic app A simple example plugin How to develop a plugin in a sane way  Now let’s get started!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Auto App</title>
      <link>/autoapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/autoapp/</guid>
      <description>  If you aren&#39;t redirected, click here     var stripe = Stripe(&#34;pk_test_6QIO1XhgLFd6FBsf556nL11Q00AaQbM3hg&#34;); var checkoutButton = document.getElementById( &#34;checkout-button-plan_F1Wy9d4JphhHv2&#34; ); function checkout() { stripe .redirectToCheckout({ items: [{ plan: &#34;plan_F1Wy9d4JphhHv2&#34;, quantity: 1 }], successUrl: window.location.protocol + &#34;//pepware.io/success&#34;, cancelUrl: window.location.protocol + &#34;//pepware.io/canceled&#34; }) .then(function(result) { if (result.error) { var displayError = document.getElementById(&#34;error-message&#34;); displayError.textContent = result.error.message; } }); } checkoutButton.addEventListener(&#34;click&#34;, checkout);  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>/excalibur_pivacy_policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/excalibur_pivacy_policy/</guid>
      <description>Excalibur Auto Body built the Excalibur Mobile app as a Commercial app. This SERVICE is provided by Excalibur Auto Body and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.
If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>/vtc_pivacy_policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/vtc_pivacy_policy/</guid>
      <description>Virginia Transportation corperation built the VTC Mobile app as a Commercial app. This SERVICE is provided by Virginia Transportation corperation and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.
If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>